all right now the inductions these six
individuals their accomplishments are
any many but people who are actually
going to be introduced to them our names
that are familiar to you their efforts
are ones that we've all felt and of
course they've made Northeast Ohio
better place so I'll be calling them up
one by one they will give their
government speakers inducting dr. Allen
Boutros is a man we all know he's part
of the leadership for our County is kind
of under county executive arm in the
beautician we'll be coming to the stage
is accomplishments we all know the
serving the second term is our county
executive for term Ohio State
Representative
he served as Speaker of the House as
well and keeping with the theme of
diversity was actually the first Jewish
representative the whole house so it's
my honor to be able to introduce you to
tonight's inductees is one of the most
influential and leaders here in Kyoto
and of course most importantly all have
to do with hospital and yesterday
opportunity to attend the groundbreaking
for the new billion dollar
transformation of the Metro campus and I
will tell you this is going to make a
huge difference in this community and
and it was a real pleasure to see the
ground break and this project to get on
the way to that project will transform
health care for the entire region
and not only health care but it's gonna
transform the near West Side it impacted
this er broad and fabulous but that's
not all he has done I mean he's been
involved in so many activities and again
I've been able to share some of those
with him he's been a leader in attacking
the opioid crisis here in Northeast Ohio
he he has been a leader in tackling a
tragic infant mortality problem we have
here and has been key a to reducing
infant mortality rate here in Northeast
Ohio because there's just one thing
after another but I only have two
minutes I have skillet berry but he's
only been here in this community as
president CEO of Metro health since 2013
yet if you look at all his
accomplishments you were the thighs
you've been here for his entire life
dr. Boutros will tell you that the most
important thing you can do is to do what
you love and clearly dr. Boutros is
doing that he clearly loves his job and
that you can see and everything he does
so I want to congratulate dr.
this award tonight and I also have a
congratulations from a close friend I
didn't know how close he was be totally
very close to you also a prior recipient
of the 2011 class I have to be the send
us congratulations algorithm thank you
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you thank you very much got the
exact computers it's a pleasure for me
to be here with all of you you know I
came to America the age of 12 and
decided to become an American decided to
do everything I can to do to become an
American and that that doesn't mean
forgetting your heritage as a matter of
fact my wife asked me Hugh she said she
thought that you I wanted us to all do
our 23andme so did our genetic testing
and it turned out I'm 99.7% Egyptian so
for those of you who don't know what
that means it means that my family
treats one Delores Trump and a couple
elites when she did her 23andme to use
Irish English French Italian Lebanese
Turkish Russians and I think I think
aside from Japanese and Australian she's
everything else
have to tell you I am delighted to be
representing the our community I'm also
delighted to be representing the mixture
of all cultures and America thank you
sir
[Applause]